Boston School of Occupational Therapy Bulletin UP139
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Boston School of Occupational Therapy Bulletin
1918 -- 2002
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Trustees of Tufts College
UP139
1.2 Linear Feet
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains the Bulletin of Boston School of Occupational Therapy from 1918 to 2002. Published by the Trustees of Tufts College, it has yearly listing of courses, requirements, and information about the school. Additional flyers and course listing may also be included with the bulletins.
Biographical / Historical
In 1851, a Board of Trustees was nominated by the subscribers to replace the temporary Board created at the 1847 Educational Convention of the Universalist Church. The new Board selected a site and drew up the governing rules for the new College.
- Boston School of Occupational Therapy [Bulletin], 1918 -- 2002; UP139.001; 1.2 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains the Bulletin of Boston School of Occupational Therapy from 1918 to 2002. It has yearly listing of courses, requirements, and information about the school. Additional flyers and course listing may also be included with the bulletins.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1918; UP139.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1921 -- 1922; UP139.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1925 -- 1926; UP139.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Boston School of Occupational Therapy - Idleness versus Mental and Physical Activity, 1926 -- 1927; UP139.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1927 -- 1928; UP139.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1929-04-15; UP139.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1930-06-01; UP139.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1932-06-01; UP139.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1934-01-01; UP139.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1936-08-01; UP139.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1938-08-01; UP139.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1940; UP139.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1943; UP139.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1944; UP139.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1945; UP139.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1949 -- 1950; UP139.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, Spring, 1951; UP139.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
  - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, Spring, 1953; UP139.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, Fall, 1954; UP139.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
  - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, Spring, 1957; UP139.001.001.00020 (Box 1)
  - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1958; UP139.001.001.00021 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1961 -- 1962; UP139.001.001.00022 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1962-08-15; UP139.001.001.00023 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1963-08-15; UP139.001.001.00024 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1964-08-15; UP139.001.001.00025 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1965 -- 1966; UP139.001.001.00026 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1966; UP139.001.001.00027 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1966 -- 1967; UP139.001.001.00028 (Box 1)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1967-08-15; UP139.001.001.00029 (Box 1)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1968 -- 1969; UP139.001.001.00030 (Box 1)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1969 -- 1970; UP139.001.001.00031 (Box 1)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1970 -- 1971; UP139.001.001.00032 (Box 1)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1971 -- 1972; UP139.001.001.00033 (Box 1)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1972 -- 1973; UP139.001.001.00034 (Box 1)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1973 -- 1974; UP139.001.001.00035 (Box 1)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1974 -- 1975; UP139.001.001.00036 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1975 -- 1976; UP139.001.001.00037 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1976 -- 1977; UP139.001.001.00038 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1977 -- 1978; UP139.001.001.00039 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1978 -- 1980; UP139.001.001.00040 (Box 1)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1981 -- 1982; UP139.001.001.00041 (Box 1)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1982 -- 1983; UP139.001.001.00042 (Box 1)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1983 -- 1984; UP139.001.001.00043 (Box 1)
  - Occupational Therapy at Tufts, 1984 -- 1985; UP139.001.001.00044 (Box 1)
  - Occupational Therapy at Tufts, 1985 -- 1986; UP139.001.001.00045 (Box 1)
  - Occupational Therapy at Tufts, 1986 -- 1987; UP139.001.001.00046 (Box 1)
  - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1989 -- 1990; UP139.001.001.00047 (Box 1)
  - Tufts - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1990 -- 1991; UP139.001.001.00048 (Box 1)
  - Tufts - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1991 -- 1992; UP139.001.001.00049 (Box 1)
  - Tufts - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1992 -- 1993; UP139.001.001.00050 (Box 1)
  - Tufts - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1993 -- 1994; UP139.001.001.00051 (Box 1)
  - Tufts - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1994 -- 1995; UP139.001.001.00052 (Box 1)
  - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1996 -- 1997; UP139.001.001.00053 (Box 1)
  - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1997 -- 1998; UP139.001.001.00054 (Box 1)
  - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1998 -- 1999; UP139.001.001.00055 (Box 1)
  - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1999 -- 2000; UP139.001.001.00056 (Box 1)
  - Tufts - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 2000 -- 2001; UP139.001.001.00057 (Box 1)
  - Tufts - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 2001 -- 2002; UP139.001.001.00058 (Box 1)
  - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1922; UP139.001.001.00059 (Box 1)
  - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1947; UP139.001.001.00060 (Box 1)
  - Tufts - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 2002; UP139.001.001.00061 (Box 1)